[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who was the first person to show that blood moved from the heart  to the lungs and back?", "correct_answer": "ibn-al-Nasif", "incorrect_answers": ["Leonardo Da Vinci", "William Harvey", "William Herschel"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was Butterfly McQueens religion?", "correct_answer": "Atheist", "incorrect_answers": ["African Methodist Episcopal", "Southern Baptist", "Northern Baptist"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which Scary Movie spoofed Airplane, The Ring, 8 Mile, Signs and American Idol?", "correct_answer": "Scary Movie 3", "incorrect_answers": ["Scary Movie", "Scary Movie 4", "Scary Movie 2"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Pregnancy has a lot of myths surrounding it. Is this one of them? Do spicy foods and/or red wine help induce labor?", "correct_answer": "No", "incorrect_answers": ["Yes"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie Cocktail, the main character played by Tom Cruise is Brian Hannigan.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In February 2004, In Romania the relatives of a dead man called Toma Petre were terrified of the thought that he had become a vampire. What did they do?", "correct_answer": "They exhumed his corpse.", "incorrect_answers": ["They hired a priest to keep an eye on his grave at night.", "All of these", "They planted garlic on his grave and all around the graveyard."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What did Mary said to Britt at the beginning of the movie Another Cinderella Story?", "correct_answer": "No thank you, Britt. Your mom is going to kill me.", "incorrect_answers": ["Now I wont get to go to the ball.", "Have you seen my skateboard?", "Wow, Britt. You put way too much makeup on this morning."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This name is of German origin and means protection.", "correct_answer": "William", "incorrect_answers": ["Robert", "George", "Richard"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie The Great Escape, the Manufacturer was the code name of Louis Sedgwick, played by James Coburn.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "A Solar Eclipse occurs when the Earth is between the Sun and the Moon.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This river is the longest in the United States, and it gave its name to one of the states.", "correct_answer": "The Missouri River", "incorrect_answers": ["The Mississippi River", "The Alabama River", "The Ohio River"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which type of chocolate is richest in fat?", "correct_answer": "Unsweetened", "incorrect_answers": ["Baking Chocolate", "Semisweet", "Bittersweet"]}]